<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <item segment="Joke-1">WHAT PANDA DOES IN A CAFE || A panda walks into a cafe. He orders a sandwich, eats it, then draws a gun and fires two shots in the air. "Why?" asks the confused waiter, as the panda makes towards the exit. The panda produces a badly punctuated wildlife manual and tosses it over his shoulder. "I'm a panda," he says, at the door. "Look it up." The waiter turns to the relevant entry and, sure enough, finds an explanation... "Panda. Large black-and-white bear-like mammal, native to China. Eats, shoots and leaves." MOTHERINLAW'S FUNERAL || A husband and wife stepped up to view the body of his mother-in-law. As he began to cry, his wife punched him and said: Why are you crying, you never liked my mother anyway. I know he replied, I thought I saw her move! MOHAMMED AND DOUGLAS ADAMS || Q: What do Mohammed and Douglas Adams have in common? A: A deep, abiding respect for the value of a towel on the head.</item>
  <item segment="Joke-2">CHINESE AND SPIELBERG || One Chinese person walks into a bar in America late one night and he saw Steven Spielberg. As he was a great fan of his movies, he rushes over to him, and asks for his autograph. Instead, Spielberg gives him a slap and says "You Chinese people bombed our Pearl Harbor, get out of here." The astonished Chinese man replied "It was not the Chinese who bombed your Pearl Harbor, it was the Japanese". "Chinese, Japanese, Taiwanese, you're all the same," replied Spielberg. In return, the Chinese gives Spielberg a slap and says "You sank the Titanic, my forefathers were on that ship." Shocked, Spielberg replies "It was the iceberg that sank the ship, not me." The Chinese replies, "Iceberg, Spielberg, Carlsberg, you're all the same."</item>
  <item segment="Joke-3">WHAT'S ON YOUR BACK? || A German, an American, and a Mexican are traveling in the Amazon, and they get captured. The head of the tribe says to the German, "What do you want on your back for your whipping?" The German responds, "I will take oil!" So they put oil on his back, and a large Amazon whips him ten times. When he is finished the German has these huge welts on his back, and he can hardly move. The Amazons haul the German away, and say to the Mexican, "What do you want on your back?" "I will take nothing!" says the Mexican, and he stands there straight and takes his ten lashings without a single flinch. "What will you take on your back?" the Amazons ask the American. He responds, "I'll take the Mexican." </item>
  <item segment="Joke-4">JUMP OUT OF THE PLANE! || An Englishman, Frenchman, Mexican, and Texan were flying across country on a small plane when the pilot comes on the loud speaker and says, "We're having mechanical problems and the only way we can make it to the next airport is for 3 of you to open the door and jump. At least one of you will survive." The four open the door and look out below. The Englishman takes a deep breath and hollers, "God Save The Queen," and jumps. The Frenchman gets really inspired and hollers, "Viva La France," and he also jumps. This really pumps up the Texan so he hollers, "Remember the Alamo," and he grabs the Mexican and throws him out of the plane. </item>
  <item segment="Joke-5">IRISH ... LIGHT BULB JOKE || How many Irishmen does it take to replace a light bulb? 30. 2.to hold the light bulb and 28 to drink till the room starts spinning. A NERD, A NUDE, AND A BIKE || A nerd was walking on campus one day when his friend, another nerd, rode up on an incredible shiny new bicycle. The first nerd was stunned and asked, "Where did you get such a nice bike?" The second nerd replied, "Well, yesterday I was walking home minding my own business when a beautiful woman rode up to me on this bike. She threw the bike to the ground, took off all her clothes and said, 'Take what you want!'" The second nerd nodded approvingly and said, "Good choice. The clothes probably wouldn't have fit."</item>
  <item segment="Joke-6">10 SIGNS YOUR AMISH TEEN'S IN TROUBLE || 10. Sometimes stays in bed till after 6 am. 9. In his sock drawer, you find pictures of women without bonnets. 8. Shows up at barn raisings in full "Kiss" makeup. 7. When you criticize him, he yells, "Thou sucketh!" 6. His name is Jebediah, but he goes by "Jeb Daddy." 5. Defiantly says, "If I had a radio, I'd listen to disco!" 4. You come upon his secret stash of colorful socks. 3. Uses slang expression: "Talk to the hand, cause the beard ain't listening." 2. Was recently pulled over for "driving under the influence of cottage cheese." 1. He's wearing his big black hat backwards.</item>
</root>
