<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <item segment="Life-1">In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on. (Robert Frost) Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment. (Buddha) A life spent making mistakes is not only more honorable, but more useful than a life spent doing nothing. (George Bernard Shaw) All life is an experiment. The more experiments you make the better. (Ralph Waldo Emerson) A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life. (Charles Darwin) Don't go around saying the world owes you a living. The world owes you nothing. It was here first. (Mark Twain) When I stand before God at the end of my life, I would hope that I would not have a single bit of talent left, and could say, 'I used everything you gave me'. (Erma Bombeck) Life is what happens while you are busy making other plans. (John Lennon) I still find each day too short for all the thoughts I want to think, all the walks I want to take, all the books I want to read, and all the friends I want to see. (John Burroughs) Believe that life is worth living and your belief will help create the fact. (William James)</item>
  <item segment="Life-2">Never be bullied into silence. Never allow yourself to be made a victim. Accept no one's definition of your life; define yourself. (Harvey Fierstein) Any idiot can face a crisis - it's day to day living that wears you out. (Anton Chekhov) Throughout life people will make you mad, disrespect you and treat you bad. Let God deal with the things they do, cause hate in your heart will consume you too. (Will Smith) A man sooner or later discovers that he is the master-gardener of his soul, the director of his life. (James Allen) Every man dies. Not every man really lives. (William Wallace) Change is the law of life. And those who look only to the past or present are certain to miss the future. (John F. Kennedy) You will never be happy if you continue to search for what happiness consists of. You will never live if you are looking for the meaning of life. (Albert Camus) I have a simple philosophy: Fill what's empty. Empty what's full. Scratch where it itches. (Alice Roosevelt Longworth) Go confidently in the direction of your dreams. Live the life you have imagined. (Henry David Thoreau)</item>
  <item segment="Life-3"> All the art of living lies in a fine mingling of letting go and holding on. (Havelock Ellis) Life is a dream for the wise, a game for the fool, a comedy for the rich, a tragedy for the poor. (Sholom Aleichem) I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day. (E. B. White) A baby is God's opinion that life should go on. (Carl Sandburg) Life is a song - sing it. Life is a game - play it. Life is a challenge - meet it. Life is a dream - realize it. Life is a sacrifice - offer it. Life is love - enjoy it. (Sai Baba) He who has a why to live can bear almost any how. (Friedrich Nietzsche) How far you go in life depends on your being tender with the young, compassionate with the aged, sympathetic with the striving and tolerant of the weak and strong. Because someday in your life you will have been all of these. (George Washington Carver) Change your life today. Don't gamble on the future, act now, without delay. (Simone de Beauvoir) Open your eyes, look within. Are you satisfied with the life you're living? (Bob Marley)</item>
  <item segment="Love-1">Love is composed of a single soul inhabiting two bodies. (Aristotle) Affection is responsible for nine-tenths of whatever solid and durable happiness there is in our lives. (C. S. Lewis) Sometimes the heart sees what is invisible to the eye. (H. Jackson Brown) Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage. (Lao Tzu) A man reserves his true and deepest love not for the species of woman in whose company he finds himself electrified and enkindled, but for that one in whose company he may feel tenderly drowsy. (George Jean Nathan) A kiss is a lovely trick designed by nature to stop speech when words become superfluous. (Ingrid Bergman) A flower cannot blossom without sunshine, and man cannot live without love. (Max Muller) Love is like a friendship caught on fire. In the beginning a flame, very pretty, often hot and fierce, but still only light and flickering. As love grows older, our hearts mature and our love becomes as coals, deep-burning and unquenchable. (Bruce Lee) Keep love in your heart. A life without it is like a sunless garden when the flowers are dead. (Oscar Wilde)</item>
  <item segment="Love-2">I have found the paradox, that if you love until it hurts, there can be no more hurt, only more love. (Mother Teresa) A woman knows the face of the man she loves as a sailor knows the open sea. (Honore de Balzac) For it was not into my ear you whispered, but into my heart. It was not my lips you kissed, but my soul. Judy Garland A loving heart is the beginning of all knowledge. (Thomas Carlyle) Immature love says: 'I love you because I need you.' Mature love says 'I need you because I love you.' (Erich Fromm) At the touch of love everyone becomes a poet. (Plato) Friends can help each other. A true friend is someone who lets you have total freedom to be yourself - and especially to feel. Or, not feel. Whatever you happen to be feeling at the moment is fine with them. That's what real love amounts to - letting a person be what he really is. (Jim Morrison) Absence diminishes mediocre passions and increases great ones, as the wind extinguishes candles and fans fires. (Francois de La Rochefoucauld) Let us always meet each other with smile, for the smile is the beginning of love. (Mother Teresa) A kiss makes the heart young again and wipes out the years. (Rupert Brooke)</item>
  <item segment="Love-3">A man is already halfway in love with any woman who listens to him. (Brendan Francis) Can miles truly separate you from friends... If you want to be with someone you love, aren't you already there? (Richard Bach) A very small degree of hope is sufficient to cause the birth of love. (Stendhal) Love begins at home, and it is not how much we do... but how much love we put in that action. (Mother Teresa) Gravitation is not responsible for people falling in love. (Albert Einstein) Come live in my heart, and pay no rent. (Samuel Lover) I have decided to stick with love. Hate is too great a burden to bear. (Martin Luther King, Jr.) We're born alone, we live alone, we die alone. Only through our love and friendship can we create the illusion for the moment that we're not alone. (Orson Welles) All love shifts and changes. I don't know if you can be wholeheartedly in love all the time. (Julie Andrews) Love does not begin and end the way we seem to think it does. Love is a battle, love is a war; love is a growing up. (James A. Baldwin) All my life, my heart has yearned for a thing I cannot name. (Andre Breton)</item>
  <item segment="Love-4">If you live to be a hundred, I want to live to be a hundred minus one day so I never have to live without you. (A. A. Milne) Where there is love there is life. (Mahatma Gandhi) Do all things with love. (Og Mandino) A part of kindness consists in loving people more than they deserve. (Joseph Joubert) As soon go kindle fire with snow, as seek to quench the fire of love with words. (William Shakespeare) Friendship often ends in love; but love in friendship - never. (Charles Caleb Colton) A loving heart is the truest wisdom. (Charles Dickens) I was born with an enormous need for affection, and a terrible need to give it. (Audrey Hepburn) A pair of powerful spectacles has sometimes sufficed to cure a person in love. (Friedrich Nietzsche) If you press me to say why I loved him, I can say no more than because he was he, and I was I. (Michel de Montaigne) Love is a force more formidable than any other. It is invisible - it cannot be seen or measured, yet it is powerful enough to transform you in a moment, and offer you more joy than any material possession could. (Barbara de Angelis) First love is only a little foolishness and a lot of curiosity. (George Bernard Shaw)</item>
  <item segment="Love-5"> Love is life. And if you miss love, you miss life. (Leo Buscaglia) Time is too slow for those who wait, too swift for those who fear, too long for those who grieve, too short for those who rejoice, but for those who love, time is eternity. (Henry Van Dyke) I was about half in love with her by the time we sat down. That's the thing about girls. Every time they do something pretty... you fall half in love with them, and then you never know where the hell you are. (J. D. Salinger) The best thing to hold onto in life is each other. (Audrey Hepburn) I like not only to be loved, but also to be told I am loved. (George Eliot) I can live without money, but I cannot live without love. (Judy Garland) If you want to be loved, be lovable. (Ovid) Love can sometimes be magic. But magic can sometimes... just be an illusion. (Javan) We loved with a love that was more than love. (Edgar Allan Poe) Love is always bestowed as a gift - freely, willingly and without expectation. We don't love to be loved; we love to love. (Leo Buscaglia) Faith makes all things possible... love makes all things easy. (Dwight L. Moody)</item>
</root>
